## **Ana Alves**

## **Digital Designer**

Digital designer with 3 years of experience in designing content for web and prototyping apps interfaces, from concept phase to the end product.

Seeking a position where I can develop and consolidate my skills, as well as learning new ones.

Portfolio:

anaalves.webflow.io/

LinkedIn:

linkedin/in/anaflipasa/

**Email:** 

anaflipasa3@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### UI/UX Designer - Polka Dot Studio, Helsinki

APRIL 2018 - JANUARY 2020

- Polished the previous UI and designed new features for *Trendy Stylist*
- Produced and managed content for *Trendy Stylist* <u>Instagram</u>
- Designed the new UI for <u>Idle Kitty: Shopkeeper</u> in collaboration with the lead artist and game designers
- Worked closely with the Dev Team by implementing the UI elements directly on Unity

### Multimedia Designer - Zappy Software, Porto

SEPTEMBER 2017 - FEBRUARY 2018

- Rebranding (Logo and illustrations for website)
- Social media management
- Prototyped the future app (wireframes + high fidelity)

#### Freelance Designer - worlDevelopers, Amsterdam

AUGUST 2015 - AUGUST 2016

- Social media management
- Helped to develop the identity of <u>CrewDNA</u> by designing the logo, flyers and social media content

#### **EDUCATION**

# **User Research - Methods and Best Practices** - *Interaction Design Foundation*

FEBRUARY 2020 - CURRENTLY

#### Msc in Multimedia - FEUP, Porto

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JULY 2017

Specialization in Technologies.

M.Sc. dissertation: "Transmedia Storytelling in B2B: the Case Study of StorySD"

advised by Prof. Soraia Ferreira. Final classification: 18/20.

**SKILLS** 

**TOOLKIT** 

Adobe XD

Figma

A. Photoshop

A. Illustrator

A. Premiere

A. After Effects

Affinity Designer

Blender

Unity

**SKILLSET** 

UI/UX Design

**Graphic Design** 

Video / Animation

Illustration

**Photography** 

Transmedia Storytelling

HTML & CSS